var questions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not JavaScript Data Types?",
    answerA: "Undefined",
    answerB: "Float",
    answerC: "Boolean",
    answerD: "Number",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the types of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?",
    answerA: "Prompt",
    answerB: "Alert",
    answerC: "Confirm",
    answerD: "All of the above",
    correctAnswer: "D",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How to write an IF statement for executing some code if 'i is NOT equal to 5'?",
    answerA: "if(i <> 5)",
    answerB: "if i <> 5",
    answerC: "if ( i != 5 )",
    answerD: "if i != 5 then",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },

  {
    question:
      'The "function" and " var" are known as:',
    answerA: "Keywords",
    answerB: "Data Types",
    answerC: "Declaration Statements",
    answerD: "Prototypes",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
    answerA: "Global Variable",
    answerB: "Local Variable",
    answerC: "All the above",
    answerD: "None of the above",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },


  {
    question:
      "Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?",
    answerA: "00",
    answerB: "0x",
    answerC: "0X",
    answerD: "Both 0x and 0X",
    correctAnswer: "D",
  },


  {
    question:
      "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
    answerA: "Syntax error",
    answerB: "Missing semicolon",
    answerC: "Division by Zero",
    answerD: "Missing bracket",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },



  {
    question:
      "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
    answerA: "toString()",
    answerB: "valueOf()",
    answerC: "toLocaleString()",
    answerD: "toPrecision()",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },


  {
    question:
      "Which of the following function of the String object returns the character in the string starting at the specified position via the specified number of characters?",
    answerA: "slice()",
    answerB: "split()",
    answerC: "substr()",
    answerD: "search()",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },


  {
    question:
      "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
    answerA: "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
    answerB: "Both are not same at all.",
    answerC: "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
    answerD: "Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
    correctAnswer: "A",
  },


  {
    question:
      "Suppose we have a text 'human' that we want to convert into string without using the new operator. Which is the correct way from the following to do so:",
    answerA: "toString()",
    answerB: "String(human)",
    answerC: "String newvariable='human'",
    answerD: "Both human.toString() and String(human)",
    correctAnswer: "D",
  },


  {
    question:
      "Which one of the following is not a keyword:",
    answerA: "if",
    answerB: "with",
    answerC: "debugger",
    answerD: "use strict",
    correctAnswer: "D",
  },

  {
    question:
      "A set of unordered properties that, has a name and value is called______",
    answerA: "String",
    answerB: "Object",
    answerC: "Array",
    answerD: "Serialized Object",
    correctAnswer: "B",
  },

  {
    question:
      "A collection of elements of the same data type which may either in order or not, is called _____.",
    answerA: "String",
    answerB: "Object",
    answerC: "Array",
    answerD: "Serialized Object",
    correctAnswer: "C",
  },


  {
    question:
      "Which one of the following method or operator is used for identification of the array?",
    answerA: "TypeOf",
    answerB: "==",
    answerC: "===",
    answerD: "Array.isArray();",
    correctAnswer: "D",
  }

];